videobull.com 2010-11-07

# Privacy Policy | VideoBloom

Your privacy is critical to us. This Privacy Policy describes how VideoBloom treats certain information provided by you in connection with your access to and use of the VideoBloom Web Site (the "Service"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to people not employed by VideoBloom or to entities not owned or controlled by VideoBloom. Information contained in or provided with Content (as that term is defined in the VideoBloom Terms and Conditions of Use) that you upload, transmit, post or otherwise make available using the Service is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the VideoBloom Terms and Conditions of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or the VideoBloom Terms and Conditions of Use, do not provide VideoBloom with any information and do not use the Service. This Privacy Policy may be modified by VideoBloom in its sole discretion at any time without prior notice to you. We will post any revised Privacy Policy on the Service. Your continued use of the Service after the Privacy Policy has been modified and posted will signify your acceptance of such modifications for information provided by you.

### 1\. Data Collection

VideoBloom, may from time to time, ask you for personal information to help serve your needs.

  * VideoBloom collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.
  * Some of our services require you to register for an account. VideoBloom asks you for some personal or company information in order to create an account and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain subscription services, we may request credit card or other payment information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers.

When we require personal information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

### 2\. Participating Merchant Policies

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in VideoBloom services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

### 3\. Information Sharing

We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of VideoBloom, its users or the public.
  * If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Privacy Policy or with your consent.
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which VideoBloom or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of VideoBloom, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

### 4\. Uses of Information Collected

We may collect personal information about you in connection with your use of the Service. Such information may include your name, company, address, telephone number, email address, IP address, biographical information and other personally identifiable information belonging to you. We may collect such information when you register with the Service and in connection with your transactions with us and some of our business partners. Our servers may automatically receive and record information about you on our server logs. We may use "cookies" containing anonymous unique identifiers stored on your computer. We may let our advertisers set and access their cookies on your computer. Our advertisers do not have access to our cookies. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. You can add or update certain information by clicking on the account settings link. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

### 5\. Data Security

We make efforts to ensure data security on our systems to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

### 6\. Information Relating to Children

The service is not structured to attract children under 13 years of age. Our Terms and Conditions of Use prohibit use of the Service by anyone under 13 years of age, and require any person providing access to the Service to anyone under 13 years of age to certify that he or she the parent or legal guardian of such person and to provide reasonable verification required by VideoBloom. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information of anyone under 13 years of age, and if we discover that we have inadvertently collected such information, we will promptly delete it. Parents and legal guardians may request us to review, delete or stop the collection of personally identifiable information of their child by contacting us at the email or postal address specified in the "Contact" section of the VideoBloom’s Web site.

### 7\. User Ability to Access, Update & Correct

Personal Information

In order to ensure that all of your Personal Information is correct and up-to-date, at any time you may visit your personal profile by logging in at our website. Through your personal profile you may: (a) review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected.

### 8\. Updates and Changes to Policy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

### 9\. Questions

If you have any questions or comments about our personal information practices or about this privacy statement, please feel free to contact us via our Web site.

### 10\. In the Event of Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy

In the event that VideoBloom is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.
